(Howard:)So, what are we gonna
name this kid?
(Howard:)Now that we know
she's a girl,
(Howard:)it kind of ruins my plan
for Wally Wolowitz.
(Bernadette:)Could name her
after your mom.
(Howard:)Debbie?
(Bernadette:)No.
(Howard:)She hated that name.
(Bernadette:)Did she have a middle name?
(Howard:)Melvina.
(Bernadette:)Let's keep thinking.
(Midwife:)Mm.
Ah.
(Howard:)It sucks that
she's not here.
(Howard:)I know.
(Howard:)Hm.
(Howard:)She would've been
the best grandma.
(Bernadette:)She did always have candy
in her pocket.
(Sheldon:)Yeah.
(Howard:)I was 20 years old
before I figured out
(Howard:)Tootsie Rolls weren't
naturally warm.
(Bernadette:)I didn't know her
five minutes and she asked,
“Are you a Milky Way
or a Snickers girl?”
(Howard:)Thank God you answered right,
we wouldn't be here today.